[Music]
Welcome to the busy central launch
edition for 2025 release wave 2. My name
is Alexander Totoich and I will show you
new ro center in the business central ro
center for account payable processes.
What what are business values for this
new functionality? We will centralize
completed workflow management related
for account payable processes from
purchase documents, e documents,
payments and all of them into one work
for us. Then definitely it will boost
productivity because uh account uh
payable teams will be simplified focus
on only one uh place for all operations
uh on a daily basis. So it will also
reduce administr effort. So they not
need to switch from one to another place
to find all documents. All documents
will be easily accessible from one RO
center.
So what account payable administrator as
a RO center will show you? First I need
to remind you this will be available for
27.1. So that means from November and
within this new RO center you can find
in all available ROS we will be focused
on completely ongoing purchase on
incoming e documents. So only incoming
parts of your documents then payments
documents approvals intercompany
processes and you will get some payable
insights there. So now I will show you
how it's looking in a demo. This is now
this new beautiful RO center account
payable and as I said you can see that
all actions are related to account
payable process. What is good we even
have all PowerBI reports related to
purchase and account payable process
here available.
So if you look all activities are
related for purchase and payment part.
So if I look for example in overdue
purchase documents you will get a list.
So everything there is related to uh uh
account payable process incoming e
documents are there. So you can see all
processed only incoming you can see all
of them are purchase invoice in a
progress all purchase documents. So
everything is there.
So I will not show you all tiles as I
said focus is on payments ongoing
purchase on e documents and inter
company you have self- service of course
part then about insights you have all my
vendors you can choose overdue purchase
documents
actually purchase invoices posted
purchase invoices and then you have nice
charts payable information payable
performance so this one is about top
five vendors
There's four different charts you can
switch to age account payable.
So you see there's different charts
different insights so you can track
easily. And now before I close this
session I would like to remind you there
are many good general business center
resources. Please remember all these
links. This is really useful and
subscribe to our LinkedIn channel so you
can track all week news announcement
from our side.
And on the end akamsbc YouTube you can
find much more videos there not only
this one and not only to this edition
for previous ones and different reasons.
So you go there and you can find all
interesting videos related to business
center. Thank you for watching this
video.